<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Landing page on Pasha&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://upav.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Landing page on Pasha&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 21:43:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://upav.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>God gave us a chance to meet</title>
      <link>https://upav.github.io/posts/1.god_gave_us_a_chance_to_meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upav.github.io/posts/1.god_gave_us_a_chance_to_meet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I was walking home with a coffee in my hand,
I was enjoing the autumn beauty of Bristol and being slightly nervous about not doing work at 11am.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll take a sick day if you don&amp;rsquo;t do anything today&amp;rdquo;, I kept telling myself.&lt;br&gt;
As I was in my head thinking about work and how beautiful everything is,
I saw a old short woman walking towards me.
As I was approaching her, she started  talking to me.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite catch the beggining of it but it quickly became:&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; these people &amp;hellip; narcotics &amp;hellip; devil city &amp;hellip; they don&amp;rsquo;t do anything about it&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br&gt;
She&amp;rsquo;s been saying a lot of words with a thick slavic accent.
Being caught by surprise and not expeting this conversation go beyond a casual two-phrase interaction,
I didn&amp;rsquo;t catch most of the things she was saying.
I guess I thought that at some point she&amp;rsquo;ll stop and
I&amp;rsquo;ll have a chance to give her a generic responce to continue my morning in the blessed silence.&lt;br&gt;
I was so naive, haha.&lt;br&gt;
Hearing she&amp;rsquo;s talking about &amp;ldquo;narcotics&amp;rdquo;,
I figured I need to start thinking of my way out of this conversation or I&amp;rsquo;ll be here for long.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog?</title>
      <link>https://upav.github.io/posts/0.blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upav.github.io/posts/0.blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the first post here I thought, I&amp;rsquo;ll go thru how and why I started writing and how it led me to creating this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing came into my life quite recently, couple of years ago, I would say.
It was when a lot of my friends started to create personal telegram channels, I thought &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Wow! This is so cool, I could do the same but don&amp;rsquo;t really know what to write about&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;.
Then during some depressive periods of my life, when I had problems understanding what exactly I feel and why I feel that way.
That was the first time the pen and paper came to the rescue!
I started asking myself questions and writing bullet point with anything that comes up.
It was the first time writing allowed me to take a step back and look at the inifinitely confusing world of me.
It worked quite well as an &amp;ldquo;energency reflection&amp;rdquo; mechanism the few times I used it, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough for me to start writing yet..&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>